keyence.com 2019-04-17

# Privacy | KEYENCE America

## Privacy Statement for our web site

KEYENCE CORPORATION of America is committed to respecting your privacy.  
We recognize it is important you know how we handle the information we receive from you on the Internet.  
We've structured our web site so that, in general, you can visit us on the web site without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information.

When you visit our web site, we may collect the domain names, not the e-mail addresses, of the visitors.  
This information is aggregated to measure the number of visitors, the time and length of your visit, the pages you look at on our site, etc.

There are also several opportunities on our web site for you to provide us with personal information about you and your interest, such as your name, mailing address and e-mail address.

If you choose to share any personal information with us, we may store it and use it for marketing research and other marketing purposes, which may include sharing it with KEYENCE CORPORATION and other KEYENCE affiliated companies of other countries. We will never sell your information to any other company.  
Further, the personal information we collect is used also by us to respond to your inquiry, process order, send the latest news and free offers or send general catalog. If you want to discontinue such subscriptions like the latest news and free offers, please request to discontinue in accordance with the procedure on our Web site.

A technology called cookies may be used to provide you with tailored information.  
A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive. So, when you return again, we can tailor information to suit your individual preferences. The goal is to save your time and provide you with a more meaningful visit. You may set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie.

KEYENCE has implemented Display Advertising and Google Analytics Remarketing to advertise online. Third-party vendors, including Google, show KEYENCE ads on sites across the internet. KEYENCE and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize and serve ads based on someone's past visits to KEYENCE's website. Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Preferences Manager.

At times we may conduct on-line surveys to better understand the needs and profile of our visitors.  
When we conduct a survey, we will try to let you know how we will use the information at the time we collect information from you on the Internet.  
Our Web site may contain links to other sites such as KEYENCE CORPORATION and other KEYENCE affiliated companies of other countries.  
While we try to link only the sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites.
